<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Projects on pennatia</title>
    <link>https://pennatia.github.io/projects/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Projects on pennatia</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en</language>
    <copyright>© 2021 Angelo Pennati</copyright>
    <lastBuildDate>Tue, 26 Mar 2019 08:47:11 +0100</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://pennatia.github.io/projects/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>Generative Art</title>
      <link>https://pennatia.github.io/projects/generative-art/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 26 Mar 2019 08:47:11 +0100</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://pennatia.github.io/projects/generative-art/</guid>
      <description>Context This Generative Art section is really more related to a passion project, which includes a few separate little explorations into the world of generative art, completed in Python.
Scope &amp;amp; Methodology Generally, the projects in the repos listed below are completed using Python&amp;rsquo;s Cairo Package, the only exception being the ASCII converter (with which the image you see on the bottom of the screen was originally created)
Here, I attempt to generate some art generatively through code, in order to create single, non-replicable vector graphics, like those you can find in the github repos.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>MNIST Modeling Project</title>
      <link>https://pennatia.github.io/projects/mnist-modeling/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 26 Mar 2019 08:47:11 +0100</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://pennatia.github.io/projects/mnist-modeling/</guid>
      <description>Context This project is an extension of the &amp;ldquo;Data Science Algorithms&amp;rdquo; repo that you can explore in the &amp;ldquo;repos&amp;rdquo; section. Essentially, it&amp;rsquo;s an exploration of the MNIST Datasets using various machine learning &amp;amp; data science methodologies, mostly built from scratch.
Scope &amp;amp; Methodology The goal of this project was to:
 Feature Reduce the MNIST Dataset Understand which features and methodologies are most useful to accurately categorize a new input image Generate a model, the analysis of which could be easily digested and understood.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Restricted Boltzmann Machine for Perceptual Organization</title>
      <link>https://pennatia.github.io/projects/computational-neuroscience-projects/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 26 Mar 2019 08:47:11 +0100</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://pennatia.github.io/projects/computational-neuroscience-projects/</guid>
      <description>Context This project was completed during my time as a Computational Neuroscience Researcher at the Ma Lab for Computational Neuroscience.
Scope &amp;amp; Methodology In short, it&amp;rsquo;s an implementation of a restricted boltzmann machine geared towards simulating a visual occlusion decision-making task. In this case, the decision is whether a line, blocked by some occlusion, is perceived as a singular line, or two separate lines.
The Restricted Boltzmann Machine is created in order to analyze different types of probabilistic models, and determine which is closest to the results seen in human trials.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Siegbrau YT (YouTube Dislike Calculator)</title>
      <link>https://pennatia.github.io/projects/siegbrau-yt/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 26 Mar 2019 08:47:11 +0100</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://pennatia.github.io/projects/siegbrau-yt/</guid>
      <description>Context This is a project initiated in conjunction with a dear friend, in an attempt to estimate the total number of dislikes associated with a given YouTube video (following YT&amp;rsquo;s elimination of the dislike button). Siegbrau is a direct reference to Dark Souls, but is a cool name and little else.
Method &amp;amp; Scope Update 1 - This project is created in Python. Initially, I created a small desktop app that essentially performs a crude version of sentiment analysis on a given video&amp;rsquo;s comment section.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
