<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Hello! on pennatia</title>
    <link>https://pennatia.github.io/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Hello! on pennatia</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en</language>
    <copyright>© 2021 Angelo Pennati</copyright>
    <lastBuildDate>Tue, 26 Mar 2019 08:47:11 +0100</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://pennatia.github.io/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>Resume</title>
      <link>https://pennatia.github.io/resume/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 08 Mar 2022 08:47:11 +0100</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://pennatia.github.io/resume/</guid>
      <description>Education  MSc in Data Science (Machine Learning &amp;amp; AI Track) \
Johns Hopkins University: Whiting School of Engineering (June 2021-present)
Current GPA: 4.30/4.30 BSc in Neural Sciences; BA in Economics
New York University: College of Arts and Sciences (2014-2018)
Cumulative GPA: 3.64/4.00 \ Presidential Honors Scholar  Professional Experience  Quantilope - Research Consultant \
Hamburg, Germany &amp;amp; New York, USA | 2021-Present 2110 - Research Analyst \ New York, USA | 2020 - 2021 SPARK Neuro - Sr.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Siegbrau YT (YouTube Dislike Calculator)</title>
      <link>https://pennatia.github.io/projects/siegbrau-yt/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 08 Mar 2022 08:47:11 +0100</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://pennatia.github.io/projects/siegbrau-yt/</guid>
      <description>Context This is a project initiated in conjunction with a dear friend, in an attempt to estimate the total number of dislikes associated with a given YouTube video (following YT&amp;rsquo;s elimination of the dislike button). Siegbrau is a direct reference to Dark Souls, but is a cool name and little else.
Method &amp;amp; Scope Update 1 - This project is created in Python. Initially, I created a small desktop app that essentially performs a crude version of sentiment analysis on a given video&amp;rsquo;s comment section.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>About</title>
      <link>https://pennatia.github.io/about/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 26 Mar 2019 08:47:11 +0100</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://pennatia.github.io/about/</guid>
      <description>Welcome to my portfolio website. I&#39;m Angelo Pennati.
 I was born in Milan (Italy) and studied Neuroscience and Economics at NYU. I am also currently pursuing an M.S. in Data Science (Machine Learning track) from Johns Hopkins University.
 I first landed in the coding world as a researcher in Weiji Ma&#39;s Computational Neuroscience Laboratory, and have continued to chase its white rabbit ever since.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Data Science Implementations &amp; Notebooks</title>
      <link>https://pennatia.github.io/repos/data-science-algorithms/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 26 Mar 2019 08:47:11 +0100</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://pennatia.github.io/repos/data-science-algorithms/</guid>
      <description>This is a repo of python code and Jupyter notebooks of multiple and various algorithms used in Data Science. Each of these projects has a self-implemented piece of code, as well as a Jupyter notebook explaining the implementation and allowing for a reference. Please use the links below to access the respective notebooks:
 Introductory Data Cleaning (Z-Scoring &amp;amp; Charting) Mahalanobis Distance Implementation Feature Reduction (2D-DCT &amp;amp; PCA) Expectation Maximization Linear Discriminant Analysis  The entirety of the repo can be found here.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Encryption Implementations</title>
      <link>https://pennatia.github.io/repos/encryption-algorithms/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 26 Mar 2019 08:47:11 +0100</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://pennatia.github.io/repos/encryption-algorithms/</guid>
      <description>This is a repo of python code of multiple algorithms used within the field of encryption. Each of these projects has a self-implemented piece of code, as well as a read-me reference. The input and output data files are also available. Please use the links below to access the respective implements:
 Frequency Analysis Encryption Hill Cypher Encryption LFSR Image Encrypter  The entirety of the repo can be found here.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Game Theory Projects</title>
      <link>https://pennatia.github.io/repos/game-theory/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 26 Mar 2019 08:47:11 +0100</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://pennatia.github.io/repos/game-theory/</guid>
      <description>This is a repo of python code of multiple algorithms used within the field of game theory and gaming. Each of these projects has a self-implemented piece of code, as well as a read-me reference. The input and output data files are also available.
So far, I have only implemented MiniMax for Tic Tac Toe. Please use the links below to access the respective implements:
 Minimax - includes TicTacToe tkinter game, with relative credits.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Generative Art</title>
      <link>https://pennatia.github.io/projects/generative-art/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 26 Mar 2019 08:47:11 +0100</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://pennatia.github.io/projects/generative-art/</guid>
      <description>Context This Generative Art section is really more related to a passion project, which includes a few separate little explorations into the world of generative art, completed in Python.
Scope &amp;amp; Methodology Generally, the projects in the repos listed below are completed using Python&amp;rsquo;s Cairo Package, the only exception being the ASCII converter (with which the image you see on the bottom of the screen was originally created)
Here, I attempt to generate some art generatively through code, in order to create single, non-replicable vector graphics, like those you can find in the github repos.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Miscellaneous Mathematics</title>
      <link>https://pennatia.github.io/repos/miscellaneous-mathematics/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 26 Mar 2019 08:47:11 +0100</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://pennatia.github.io/repos/miscellaneous-mathematics/</guid>
      <description>This is a repo of python code of multiple algorithms for miscellaneous concepts in number theory. Each of these projects has a self-implemented piece of code, as well as a read-me reference. The input and output data files are also available.
 Catalan Numbers Pascal Numbers  </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>MNIST Modeling Project</title>
      <link>https://pennatia.github.io/projects/mnist-modeling/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 26 Mar 2019 08:47:11 +0100</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://pennatia.github.io/projects/mnist-modeling/</guid>
      <description>Context This project is an extension of the &amp;ldquo;Data Science Algorithms&amp;rdquo; repo that you can explore in the &amp;ldquo;repos&amp;rdquo; section. Essentially, it&amp;rsquo;s an exploration of the MNIST Datasets using various machine learning &amp;amp; data science methodologies, mostly built from scratch.
Scope &amp;amp; Methodology The goal of this project was to:
 Feature Reduce the MNIST Dataset Understand which features and methodologies are most useful to accurately categorize a new input image Generate a model, the analysis of which could be easily digested and understood.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Restricted Boltzmann Machine for Perceptual Organization</title>
      <link>https://pennatia.github.io/projects/computational-neuroscience-projects/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 26 Mar 2019 08:47:11 +0100</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://pennatia.github.io/projects/computational-neuroscience-projects/</guid>
      <description>Context This project was completed during my time as a Computational Neuroscience Researcher at the Ma Lab for Computational Neuroscience.
Scope &amp;amp; Methodology In short, it&amp;rsquo;s an implementation of a restricted boltzmann machine geared towards simulating a visual occlusion decision-making task. In this case, the decision is whether a line, blocked by some occlusion, is perceived as a singular line, or two separate lines.
The Restricted Boltzmann Machine is created in order to analyze different types of probabilistic models, and determine which is closest to the results seen in human trials.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
