<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Repos on pennatia</title>
    <link>https://pennatia.github.io/repos/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Repos on pennatia</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en</language>
    <copyright>© 2021 Angelo Pennati</copyright>
    <lastBuildDate>Tue, 26 Mar 2019 08:47:11 +0100</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://pennatia.github.io/repos/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>Data Science Implementations &amp; Notebooks</title>
      <link>https://pennatia.github.io/repos/data-science-algorithms/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 26 Mar 2019 08:47:11 +0100</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://pennatia.github.io/repos/data-science-algorithms/</guid>
      <description>This is a repo of python code and Jupyter notebooks of multiple and various algorithms used in Data Science. Each of these projects has a self-implemented piece of code, as well as a Jupyter notebook explaining the implementation and allowing for a reference. Please use the links below to access the respective notebooks:
 Introductory Data Cleaning (Z-Scoring &amp;amp; Charting) Mahalanobis Distance Implementation Feature Reduction (2D-DCT &amp;amp; PCA) Expectation Maximization Linear Discriminant Analysis  The entirety of the repo can be found here.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Encryption Implementations</title>
      <link>https://pennatia.github.io/repos/encryption-algorithms/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 26 Mar 2019 08:47:11 +0100</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://pennatia.github.io/repos/encryption-algorithms/</guid>
      <description>This is a repo of python code of multiple algorithms used within the field of encryption. Each of these projects has a self-implemented piece of code, as well as a read-me reference. The input and output data files are also available. Please use the links below to access the respective implements:
 Frequency Analysis Encryption Hill Cypher Encryption LFSR Image Encrypter  The entirety of the repo can be found here.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Game Theory Projects</title>
      <link>https://pennatia.github.io/repos/game-theory/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 26 Mar 2019 08:47:11 +0100</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://pennatia.github.io/repos/game-theory/</guid>
      <description>This is a repo of python code of multiple algorithms used within the field of game theory and gaming. Each of these projects has a self-implemented piece of code, as well as a read-me reference. The input and output data files are also available.
So far, I have only implemented MiniMax for Tic Tac Toe. Please use the links below to access the respective implements:
 Minimax - includes TicTacToe tkinter game, with relative credits.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Miscellaneous Mathematics</title>
      <link>https://pennatia.github.io/repos/miscellaneous-mathematics/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 26 Mar 2019 08:47:11 +0100</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://pennatia.github.io/repos/miscellaneous-mathematics/</guid>
      <description>This is a repo of python code of multiple algorithms for miscellaneous concepts in number theory. Each of these projects has a self-implemented piece of code, as well as a read-me reference. The input and output data files are also available.
 Catalan Numbers Pascal Numbers  </description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
